{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which is HTML-like Syntax commonly used in React Applications?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": ["TypeScript", "CoffeeScript", "JSX", "JSON"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do component names have to start with Capital letter?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "Because of TypeScript",
        "To avoid Bugs",
        "To avoid confusion with regular HTML elements",
        "None of the Above"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of the object we use to pass down data from parent to children?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": ["state", "props", "hooks", "event"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the purpose of interpolation brackets?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "To execute bits of JavaScript within JSX",
        "To facilitate data flow",
        "To access the state",
        "To handle the events"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What does setState function do?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "Mutates existing state",
        "Merges existing state with the new state",
        "Deletes the State",
        "Creates a new state"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hook is the alternative to lifecycle methods?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "useRef",
        "useState",
        "useEffect",
        "None of the Above"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the biggest advantage of UI components?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "Simplicity",
        "Reusability",
        "Easy to design",
        "Other"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Can Functional components have a state, and how?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "They can't",
        "They can, using lifecycle methods",
        "They can, using Web API",
        "They can, using React hooks"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which file lists all the project dependencies?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "App.js",
        "package.json",
        "index.js",
        "App.css"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What arguments does useEffect function accept?",
      "multipleChoiceAnswers": [
        "The state object",
        "External url",
        "String",
        "function, array"
      ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3
    }
  ]
}
